wikicfp.com 2017-12-13

# WikiCFP : Call For Papers of Conferences, Workshops and Journals

### PRIVACY POLICY - COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At WikiCFP.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. 

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

### INFORMATION WikiCFP.com GATHERS AND TRACKS

WikiCFP.com gathers two types of information about users: 

1\. Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to take advantege of our web service. 

2\. Information WikiCFP.com gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does WikiCFP.com divulge any information about an individual user to a third party. 

We require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users. Users must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address. 

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

WikiCFP.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. WikiCFP.com does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). 

WikiCFP.com sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. WikiCFP.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to use the web service. 

### USE OF INFORMATION

WikiCFP.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to enable users to take advantage of the web service. WikiCFP.com never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners. 

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

WikiCFP.com creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

### SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

WikiCFP.com uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will NOT share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

### YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by WikiCFP.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
